{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015829772","data":{"timestamp":" 947015829772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" f670be04-112d-45eb-830e-eecacf94890f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015849397","data":{"timestamp":" 947015849397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b7fd7b7e-28ff-4de5-9b57-0fa8d143a3ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015855534","data":{"timestamp":" 947015855533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b7fd7b7e-28ff-4de5-9b57-0fa8d143a3ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015875540","data":{"timestamp":" 947015875539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b7fd7b7e-28ff-4de5-9b57-0fa8d143a3ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015883656","data":{"timestamp":" 947015883656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b7fd7b7e-28ff-4de5-9b57-0fa8d143a3ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015888963","data":{"timestamp":" 947015888963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b7fd7b7e-28ff-4de5-9b57-0fa8d143a3ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015897306","data":{"timestamp":" 947015897306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b7fd7b7e-28ff-4de5-9b57-0fa8d143a3ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015916393","data":{"timestamp":" 947015916393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 9fa87194-f526-439d-9ae5-7410a247e078"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015925475","data":{"timestamp":" 947015925474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 9fa87194-f526-439d-9ae5-7410a247e078"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015935000","data":{"timestamp":" 947015934999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 9fa87194-f526-439d-9ae5-7410a247e078"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015944498","data":{"timestamp":" 947015944498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 9fa87194-f526-439d-9ae5-7410a247e078"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015952333","data":{"timestamp":" 947015952332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 9fa87194-f526-439d-9ae5-7410a247e078"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015960931","data":{"timestamp":" 947015960931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 9fa87194-f526-439d-9ae5-7410a247e078"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8+0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015973367","data":{"timestamp":" 947015973367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 9fa87194-f526-439d-9ae5-7410a247e078"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015980363","data":{"timestamp":" 947015980363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 9fa87194-f526-439d-9ae5-7410a247e078"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015987202","data":{"timestamp":" 947015987202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 9fa87194-f526-439d-9ae5-7410a247e078"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947015995646","data":{"timestamp":" 947015995646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 9fa87194-f526-439d-9ae5-7410a247e078"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016004897","data":{"timestamp":" 947016004896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 9fa87194-f526-439d-9ae5-7410a247e078"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016016518","data":{"timestamp":" 947016016517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016018323","data":{"timestamp":" 947016018323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016020331","data":{"timestamp":" 947016020331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016022591","data":{"timestamp":" 947016022591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016026330","data":{"timestamp":" 947016026330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016028246","data":{"timestamp":" 947016028246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016030896","data":{"timestamp":" 947016030896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016034400","data":{"timestamp":" 947016034400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016036335","data":{"timestamp":" 947016036335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016038324","data":{"timestamp":" 947016038324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016040823","data":{"timestamp":" 947016040822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016044508","data":{"timestamp":" 947016044507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016046748","data":{"timestamp":" 947016046748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016048796","data":{"timestamp":" 947016048796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016051910","data":{"timestamp":" 947016051909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016055334","data":{"timestamp":" 947016055334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016057215","data":{"timestamp":" 947016057215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016060512","data":{"timestamp":" 947016060512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016063401","data":{"timestamp":" 947016063400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016066413","data":{"timestamp":" 947016066413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016069193","data":{"timestamp":" 947016069193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016071542","data":{"timestamp":" 947016071542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016074313","data":{"timestamp":" 947016074312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016077874","data":{"timestamp":" 947016077874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016079995","data":{"timestamp":" 947016079995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016082132","data":{"timestamp":" 947016082132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016083912","data":{"timestamp":" 947016083911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016086669","data":{"timestamp":" 947016086669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016089929","data":{"timestamp":" 947016089928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016091914","data":{"timestamp":" 947016091914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016093999","data":{"timestamp":" 947016093999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016098416","data":{"timestamp":" 947016098416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016101384","data":{"timestamp":" 947016101384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016103081","data":{"timestamp":" 947016103081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016104911","data":{"timestamp":" 947016104911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016106673","data":{"timestamp":" 947016106673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016108768","data":{"timestamp":" 947016108768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016110758","data":{"timestamp":" 947016110758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016112324","data":{"timestamp":" 947016112324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016114413","data":{"timestamp":" 947016114413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016116786","data":{"timestamp":" 947016116785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016118890","data":{"timestamp":" 947016118890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016120773","data":{"timestamp":" 947016120773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016120897","data":{"timestamp":" 947016120896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016123800","data":{"timestamp":" 947016123800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016126321","data":{"timestamp":" 947016126321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016129980","data":{"timestamp":" 947016129980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016132504","data":{"timestamp":" 947016132504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016134131","data":{"timestamp":" 947016134131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016136154","data":{"timestamp":" 947016136153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016136315","data":{"timestamp":" 947016136315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016145426","data":{"timestamp":" 947016145426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" b59e264e-6c9e-47f5-8585-e76694130d2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016157344","data":{"timestamp":" 947016157343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016158827","data":{"timestamp":" 947016158827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016160989","data":{"timestamp":" 947016160989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016162719","data":{"timestamp":" 947016162719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016165093","data":{"timestamp":" 947016165092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016167225","data":{"timestamp":" 947016167225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016169157","data":{"timestamp":" 947016169157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016171385","data":{"timestamp":" 947016171385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016173078","data":{"timestamp":" 947016173078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016175520","data":{"timestamp":" 947016175520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016181619","data":{"timestamp":" 947016181618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016183578","data":{"timestamp":" 947016183577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016185427","data":{"timestamp":" 947016185426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016187683","data":{"timestamp":" 947016187682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016190126","data":{"timestamp":" 947016190125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016194050","data":{"timestamp":" 947016194050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016195732","data":{"timestamp":" 947016195732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016197454","data":{"timestamp":" 947016197454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016198046","data":{"timestamp":" 947016198046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947016198228","data":{"timestamp":" 947016198228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017090702","data":{"timestamp":" 947017090702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017104896","data":{"timestamp":" 947017104896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017112964","data":{"timestamp":" 947017112964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 41ca0e0c-0634-47aa-b463-f6994132aa06"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017137652","data":{"timestamp":" 947017137652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 240d7953-b0ba-402f-ab00-426398eb4587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017147230","data":{"timestamp":" 947017147230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 240d7953-b0ba-402f-ab00-426398eb4587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017154203","data":{"timestamp":" 947017154202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 240d7953-b0ba-402f-ab00-426398eb4587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017167720","data":{"timestamp":" 947017167719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 240d7953-b0ba-402f-ab00-426398eb4587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017180456","data":{"timestamp":" 947017180455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 240d7953-b0ba-402f-ab00-426398eb4587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017188269","data":{"timestamp":" 947017188269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 240d7953-b0ba-402f-ab00-426398eb4587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017195029","data":{"timestamp":" 947017195028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 240d7953-b0ba-402f-ab00-426398eb4587"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017213874","data":{"timestamp":" 947017213874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 0f643925-bf0c-42f3-94f7-91d38c10f98c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017222462","data":{"timestamp":" 947017222462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 0f643925-bf0c-42f3-94f7-91d38c10f98c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017226946","data":{"timestamp":" 947017226946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 0f643925-bf0c-42f3-94f7-91d38c10f98c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017238495","data":{"timestamp":" 947017238495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 75ede53c-eea4-4e34-bb5b-1d7056ebe62f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017239167","data":{"timestamp":" 947017239166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 75ede53c-eea4-4e34-bb5b-1d7056ebe62f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017250925","data":{"timestamp":" 947017250924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017253385","data":{"timestamp":" 947017253385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017253593","data":{"timestamp":" 947017253593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017254322","data":{"timestamp":" 947017254322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017257162","data":{"timestamp":" 947017257161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEKA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017257902","data":{"timestamp":" 947017257902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NUKTA"," userResponse":" NUKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017258692","data":{"timestamp":" 947017258691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017258870","data":{"timestamp":" 947017258870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017259777","data":{"timestamp":" 947017259777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SENTENSI"," userResponse":" SENTENSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017261893","data":{"timestamp":" 947017261892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017262559","data":{"timestamp":" 947017262558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFANO"," userResponse":" MFANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017265131","data":{"timestamp":" 947017265131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017265513","data":{"timestamp":" 947017265513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017266565","data":{"timestamp":" 947017266565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROBOTUTOR"," userResponse":" ROBOTUTOR"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017269243","data":{"timestamp":" 947017269243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017269362","data":{"timestamp":" 947017269362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 30dc8fd3-fafb-443a-9f71-ea4a02fbb73b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROBOTUTOR"," userResponse":" ROBOTUTOR"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017281518","data":{"timestamp":" 947017281518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017283947","data":{"timestamp":" 947017283945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017284158","data":{"timestamp":" 947017284158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017284889","data":{"timestamp":" 947017284887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017287695","data":{"timestamp":" 947017287694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEKA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017288454","data":{"timestamp":" 947017288453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NUKTA"," userResponse":" NUKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017289245","data":{"timestamp":" 947017289244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017289422","data":{"timestamp":" 947017289421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017290331","data":{"timestamp":" 947017290331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SENTENSI"," userResponse":" SENTENSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017292464","data":{"timestamp":" 947017292464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017293130","data":{"timestamp":" 947017293130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFANO"," userResponse":" MFANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017295730","data":{"timestamp":" 947017295730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017296111","data":{"timestamp":" 947017296110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017297140","data":{"timestamp":" 947017297140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROBOTUTOR"," userResponse":" ROBOTUTOR"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017299915","data":{"timestamp":" 947017299914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017300067","data":{"timestamp":" 947017300066"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROBOTUTOR"," userResponse":" ROBOTUTOR"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017306003","data":{"timestamp":" 947017306002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" c9d96c7e-ee0d-40cc-91b0-bb75a52d95b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hii ni RoboTutor."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017317544","data":{"timestamp":" 947017317544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 8277e0d2-5e64-486c-907e-86ee51773dbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::kituo","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017318084","data":{"timestamp":" 947017318083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 8277e0d2-5e64-486c-907e-86ee51773dbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017318216","data":{"timestamp":" 947017318215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 8277e0d2-5e64-486c-907e-86ee51773dbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017325927","data":{"timestamp":" 947017325927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 8277e0d2-5e64-486c-907e-86ee51773dbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_1.punc.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017339791","data":{"timestamp":" 947017339790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 8277e0d2-5e64-486c-907e-86ee51773dbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_1.punc.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017364312","data":{"timestamp":" 947017364312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 8277e0d2-5e64-486c-907e-86ee51773dbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947017372281","data":{"timestamp":" 947017372281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_225703"," gameId":" 8277e0d2-5e64-486c-907e-86ee51773dbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__kituo"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}